[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Don’t worry, my love.
I’ll take care of the children.
Rest now, my love.
We’ll see each other again. Just wait for me.
Oh, Mom.
To the father of all of you.
Viktor and Donabel escaped!
That’s not even the bad news, yet.
We have reason to believe
that they’ve already left the country.
What?
You’re making the wrong decision.
Didn’t you two already plan a life together?
What happened?
We all know there’s really no future for Mikoy and me.
I can’t escape who I really am.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ GENERAL
Mikoy.
Mikoy, where are you going?
If I'm not mistaken,
I am no longer a police asset of this agency.
You don't get to run my life anymore.
I understand what you're feeling.
Really?
You have no idea
what I'm going through.
Stop acting like you're the only one who lost someone they loved.
You're not the only one who's hurting.
You're not the only one who lost a family member.
And you're not the only one who became a victim of injustice.
Look at what I did with myself.
I didn't wallow in self-pity.
I didn't let my anger consume me.
I entered the system,
and I tried to make the system work,
so I could get the justice I was looking for.
Did you get it?
Did you get justice for your father?
Did you find the person who killed him?
Did you make the people who did this to you and your family pay?
You're right.
I didn’t.
But every day that I do this,
I pray for just one thing.
That no one else gets dragged into this,
that no one else has to experience
the injustice that I experienced.
And I promised myself, Mikoy,
that I would never ever take the law into my own hands.
Because that's not true justice.
It only spreads the same violence even further,
the very violence that victimized my father and my family.
So please, Mikoy,
don't do something you'll regret in the end.
Yes, you're right.
Let's get justice for Dad Mario's death.
But let's do it the right way.
Because I'm sure
that's what he would want too.
Our top priority is figuring out how to control the Concordat.
Yes, a lot of them have switched sides and are supporting us,
but there are still many who are fighting back.
Especially Rio de Janyx's faction.
What are you going to do?
I'm going back to the Philippines for now.
To make sure Rahmboy has cleaned up everything.
Don't tell me you're going to miss me.
There's just one more obstacle to my leadership of the Concordat.
Who?
Move over.
Relax. Come on, come on.
Relax. We're not the enemy.
If you're not the enemy, why are you following me?
What do you want?
Just a second.
I'm just getting my wallet.
Here, here.
BUREAU OF INTELLIGENCE AND BLACK OPERATIONS
BIBO?
I think we're the ones who can help with your problem.
Hey, not too fast.
What do you mean?
If you really want to get justice for your father's death,
call me.
We're the agency
that operates in the shadows.
We're also the agency
that can bend the rules.
Where are you?
So you'd better tell me where you are.
And another thing, you are not a queen.
So you think we’re still redeemable, huh?
Between the two of us, I thought I was the naive one.
But I guess I was wrong.
And the more you hide,
the more reason you give me to believe
that you're not on my side.
Donatello, you won't beat me.
So here's your only choice.
Family, sibling, or whatever you want to call it.
Or I'll hunt you down myself.
It can't be that I'm the only one who's heartbroken in this story.
I'm on my way back.
Okay, we have a big problem.
What kind of problem?
If you really want to get justice for your father's death,
call me.
We're the agency that can operate in the shadows.
We're also the agency that can bend the rules.
Mikoy?
Mikoy and I are getting married.
Looks like you learned a lot from Chiara.
Do you know all of this?
If there's one thing impressive about you,
it's your loyalty to her.
No one can stop me.
Until I get justice for my father's death.
I don't care if all of you and your minions join forces.
Because I'll wipe you all out.
Until people like you no longer exist in this world.
If you're going to kill me, Chiara, or anyone else,
it won't make the pain you're feeling go away.
Before you go down this path, my friend,
is this really what you want?
The day she killed my father.
Hello, Mom?
Hello, son, Mikoy.
Where are you?
Don't you have work?
I do, Mom. I'm here in Manila.
What?
What are you doing there?
Is this because of your father?
No, Mom.
This isn't about Dad.
Oh.
If not, why are you there without telling me?
Are you craving floods, son?
Pothole-filled roads and pollution?
Is that what you're looking for?
Come on, Mom.
Not all the roads here are full of potholes.
Besides, they're just a little bumpy.
And it's not exactly pollution.
Can't it just be foggy, Mom?
Oh, you.
It's the same thing. You just said it differently.
Don't try to dodge the question.
Why are you there?
I just had to take care of something
as a tourism officer in Albay.
I'm joining a…
travel expo next month.
I'm just going to showcase the beauty of Albay.
We can't be the only ones who get to see how beautiful it is, right?
Mom.
Please believe me.
I'm really okay.
And yes, I really am working here.
Okay, Mom?
What do you mean?
Just yesterday, he got connected with BIBO.
Who are these BIBOs?
Their M.O. is simple.
And they operate off the record and unofficially for the government.
Because with so many bad people, criminals,
the law can't keep up with all of them.
So because of their power and protection,
this group was formed.
I'm just worried and afraid
that if they manage to get Mikoy on their side,
Chiara won't be the only one in danger,
you won't be the only one in danger,
the whole squad will be in danger.
Chiara specifically instructed us not to make a move against Mikoy.
If anything happens to Mikoy,
we'll be the ones who take the hit.
Unless you can make it look like an accident.
I don’t care if it’s not fine or if it’s wrong.
All I know is that
I love you so much.
And it doesn’t matter
if the whole world is angry at you.
I will face them all for you.
Seriously?
La Fornarina?
Asking someone to open a water bottle?
Even if I'm the infamous La Fornarina,
the deadliest,
most powerful assassin in the world,
I'm still a woman,
standing in front of a boy,
asking him to open my water bottle!
Or I will snap your neck
and send you to an early grave!
Okay, okay. Here, here.
I'm opening it.
Come on, sweetheart. Don't threaten me.
See? It's that easy.
-Exactly. -Thank you, sweetheart.
Let me have a little.
I hope you're doing well.
I hope you're eating properly, my love.
And I hope
you don't let your anger consume you too much.
Yes, yes.
Just finish your breakfast, you two.
No, Cocoy and Carlota, you're still new to the force, so you don't know.
But this is Janggo,
from the Bureau of Intelligence and Black Operations, or BIBO
Those people who work in the shadows.
All we offer is an additional tool for the government
for dealing with criminals who have escaped our justice system.
We don't neutralize people just for the sake of neutralizing them.
We only do this when it's necessary to make them pay for their crimes,
and to make sure they can't hurt anyone again.
Is that what you tell yourself to justify killings?
To get the justice I've been looking for?
Now it's up to you and the entire agency
whether you want to be part of this decision.
She already victimized my father.
And I won't let that happen to anyone else.
Even we are tired of this slow justice.
A true brother.
But in our world,
BIBO is a legitimate agency,
and they are legal.
From this moment on,
When Chiara took her seat as the Queen of the Concordat,
the organization regained its strength.
All of their operations are in Europe.
But sooner or later, they will reach the Philippines too.
And to prevent that from happening,
we have to neutralize Chiara.
Your mother respects you.
But that doesn’t mean I will extend that same courtesy to you.
What makes you say that?
Because Bro Mikoy has one thing that you don’t.
And what is that?
He has a reason to live.
Mikoy.
We have new information.